[{"answer": "I think the act was cowardly, and it was terrorism.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Why do they do what they do?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, the Russians were concerned, otherwise they wouldn't have reached out.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "And they can talk their way around the houses on this, but that's what we're left with, isn't it, Jake?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, you're right, Piers.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Is that relevant or was this all centered, perhaps around some radical extremists that he met when he was in Dagestan?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Incredibly itinerant parents and family.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Do we read anything sinister into their activities?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Piers, I don't think people should leap to that conclusion.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Has this just been a massive ball dropped collectively by the FBI and now the CIA?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "And it would certainly seemed to me there were plenty of grounds to the very least have an inquiry, isn't it?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "It's systemic, absolutely.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "I mean, has there been a fairly catastrophic intelligence failure here?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, you know, \"Inspire\" magazine had a specific issue devoted to how to make a device out of a pressure cooker.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "But you've got to say the former is the more realistic, isn't it?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I think the last thing the Russian authorities are likely to do at this point is to reveal whether it's true or whether it's simply speculation that something could have been done on their part to stop the attack.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Will the Russian authorities be that keen to try and establish that this could all have been predicated by activity in Dagestan?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I think it's a very disconcerting message.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Mitch Silber, if it isn't the case of Tamerlan Tsarnaev going back home to Dagestan, getting into bed with messy terrorist-related people, and then coming back with his new tricks and blowing up the marathon -- if it turns out that he and his brother were self radicalized right in the middle of Boston, what is that going to send as a message to the American people going forward?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Bob Baer, this mysterious Misha, the family friend of the Tsarnaevs, that the two brothers' family insist was more to do with the radicalizing of Tamerlan -- he's of Armenian descent, a recent convert to Islam.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "How deep is the American public going to allow intelligence agencies and law enforcement to try and detect it before we have a Boston type event?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "I think that almost inevitably it's a combination of the Internet, reading the newspapers and some sort of influence of somebody who has been through this and thought through it and talked about the justice of it.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Could this be a complete red herring, or could there be some merit to the argument that it was somebody like that over here that radicalized this young man's head?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "First, thanks for having us.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Do either of you know whether that may be your brother?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Our family and friends have been working tirelessly, night and day, looking everywhere for him, getting the word out, alongside the police-led investigation.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Have you any idea what may have happened to him or why he disappeared?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "He never was clinically diagnosed.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yeah, it was incredibly painful for our family.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Sangeeta, what was your reaction when you heard what was happening on social media, was driving it?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "They were.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "They were calling your brother a bomber, weren't they?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, I would say to him that we love him, and we miss him greatly.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "If it is not he, and he is still out there somewhere, and by chance maybe watching this interview right now, what would you like to say?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Just pointing out the hypocrisy of the left, how they push for gun control ten seconds after Sandy Hook shooting.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Why did you do this?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "You can cook food.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "What other things can you do with a pressure cooker other than kill people?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Other than shooting.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What other things can you do with a gun other than shoot things?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "You.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "You use a gun as a walking stick, do you?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, I'm likening it into the impossibility of controlling someone's actions just because -- or thinking their actions are controlled by inanimate objects.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "You're likening spoons to guns?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "No, what I'm saying is people who -- like yourself who try to perpetrate that a gun, an inanimate object is actually what killed the people, instead of saying it was the person with the gun, is very similar to someone saying, a bomb killed someone, instead of a person who constructed a bomb and blew it up.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Is that what you're telling me, senator?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "That's statistically what's always proven to be the case.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Do you believe that the answer to gun violence is that more people should be armed?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "They did a buyback.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "So you're in favor of taking everyone's guns away?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "I love the Australia plan.", "docId": "130424pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Like the Australia plan?", "qSentId": 510}]